A complete workflow from image generation
to editing and archiving.
We begin with a new task in Codex,
then generate images directly on the Cowart canvas.
Three different visual styles appear in sequence.
Each image can be selected, moved, resized,
and rearranged directly on the canvas.
Once generation is complete,
every asset is automatically added to MOSA.
The gallery brings all results together,
while preserving the prompt, model, dimensions, and source.
Next, we return to Codex and create
architectural, fashion, and material studies.
Different formats and mediums all remain
part of the same workflow.
Each artwork can be opened on its own
and reviewed in detail.
Refine it further, or save it directly
to the library.
Finally, MOSA reconnects the work
created across Codex and Cowart,
while keeping every source and parameter traceable.
From generation and editing
to archiving and reuse,
the entire creative pipeline is complete.